A variety of warriors gather at Babylon.
Mercenaries, well-practiced at combat...
former holy knights, and people
with grudges against the holy knights.
If you're strong enough, your faults
will be forgiven here in Babylon.
In other words, they need all the
help they can get to deal with the monsters.
Sounds like a perfect place for me.
The Guardian Of Lust
I'm Northern Alistair.
It's an honor to serve the heir to one of
the five great families, Lady Roxy.
In my father's absence, you were
responsible for Babylon's order, then?
Thank you for your service.
No. I was unable to save Sir Mason,
despite serving at his side...
For that, I am sorry.
You were there when he passed?
Yes.
Raise your head, Northern.
I have come here in order to
follow in my father's footsteps.
Let us defend Galia from the incursion
of monsters and defend the people.
Yes.
He's making eyes at Lady Roxy!
Her chastity is in danger!
I better get in there and save her!
Stay put, stupid.
You mess with a holy knight,
and it'll be your head.
But he's buzzing around her like a pest!
Mugan, Miria. Let's take a look at the town.
Right!
Ten gold coins for a room...
a gold coin for breakfast...
No amount of money would be
enough in this place.
Hold it, Fate. Look on your left.
That scabbard is calling to me!
It looks ridiculously expensive...
Don't be such a cheapskate!
You can always hunt monsters for more money.
Welcome! Looking for something—
Look at that!
What?!
These aren't regular burns, are they?
They were caused by Fireball...
No, probably something even hotter.
You can tell?
Was I right? Well, now!
This guy's got a real eye for detail.
We can trust his work.
We're buying a scabbard from him, Fate.
Come on!
How much does this scabbard go for?
Oh, it's just a display model.
If you want a scabbard,
I'll make one that suits your sword.
This is the sword.
Hey there.
I've never seen a one-handed sword like this!
It's incredible!
You hear that, Fate?!
Looks like quality recognizes quality.
And my glory is so obvious,
you couldn't hide it if you tried!
If you're looking for a scabbard
that'd match a sword like this...
I'd price that at around 500 gold coins.
F-Five hundred gold?!
N-Never mind!
Looks like we need to build a war chest.
Dammit, 500 gold coins?
That's practically robbery.
Prices are high enough in Babylon.
We can't spend that much on luxuries!
First, we need to cover our daily expenses.
Hey there, warrior in the skull mask.
Care to join up with us?
You wanna build your rep on a monster hunt,
so you can go work as a volunteer
soldier in the capital, right?
No thanks. I'm not looking
to work with anyone.
That's... uh, my apologies.
I'd imagine that means...
you're an ex-knight, then?
You just, uh, didn't look too
put-together, so I assumed...
Pardon us!
Come on, let's move!
Right!
Well, excuse me for looking shabby.
See? If you dressed decently, you wouldn't
have goons like them messing with you.
I guess appearances are a part
of your defense after all...
If we're putting a look together,
let's make it a good one!
Oh, yeah!
In that case, let's hunt a bunch of beasts
and earn a bunch of money!
Past the border is Galia.
It smells awful...
Yeah, there's monster carcasses all over.
What the—?
Spores.
From the moss?
Yep. Its spores are mildly toxic.
I wouldn't breathe too much
of them if I were you.
Would it kill you to warn me earlier?
If you take too many deep breaths,
moss will grow in your lungs.
Don't freak out. That's just how Galia is.
This is Galia...
And it looks like there's a minor
stampede already on the way.
Where?
Orcs, a type of monster
that are spread all over Galia.
They arm themselves with simple weapons.
Looks like around 50 of them.
They're smart, so they'll use
a coordinated attack.
I'd approach this like
you're fighting humans.
Got it.
This'll be a chance to show off
the fighting skills Aaron taught me!
Go!
They took the initiative.
What're you doing, you idiot?!
Shut up!
Just get in there and steal the kills, Fate!
So I can get that fancy scabbard!
Come on, that'd be bad etiquette!
There's no etiquette or rules
to hunting monsters, man!
Are those... more orcs?
A lot, too. Looks to be
about two companies' worth.
They're aiming for a pincer attack.
Then we won't be stealing these kills.
Yep. A great chance for you
to play hero yet again, Fate.
You ready, Greed?
You bet!
So, how do you like my third level?
Completely blocks physical and magic attacks.
This magic shield is practically a fortress.
You're welcome to start
with the praise, Fate.
Shut up! We're in the middle of a fight.
Pipe down.
Now what do I do...?
Just rush them, Fate.
I'll show you why this shield's so huge.
Go on, start running and don't stop!
Got it!
This is amazing...
Gluttony skill has activated.
This is Shield Bash.
It takes quite a bit of strength, which
shouldn't be a problem for you right now.
Keep on going!
All right!
Anyone hungry for mashed pork?
That's just nasty! Show a little tact!
Gluttony skill has activated.
[Stats]
Vitality:
Strength:
Magic:
Spirit:
Agility:
[Skills]
Gluttony, Identify, Telepathy
Conceal, Night Vision, Brawler,
Holy Sword Technique
One-Handed Sword Technique,
Two-Handed Sword Technique
Strength Boost (Low)
Strength Boost (Med)
Strength Boost (Large)
Vitality Boost (Low)
Vitality Boost  (Med)
Agility Boost (Med)
Health Regen
Fireball
Illusion
Fire Resistance
Magic Boost (Large)
Spirit Boost (Large)
What's up?
My Gluttony skill isn't acting up...
Even after beating so many orcs.
Has it been like that
since you took down Haniel?
Yeah...
Could this control be
what Aaron was training me for?
Let's clip these orc ears
and get back to town.
Yeah, I know.
Are you kidding me? Are those all orc ears?
That would be enough
for two whole companies...
And he did it by himself?
I'd like to cash these in.
I-I'll confirm the number right away.
Hey, punk! You think you can swoop in
and steal our loot like that?
Those belong to us!
You guys would've been turned
to mush if it wasn't for Fate.
Hand them over!
Don't.
This is your last chance to back off.
I'd like to see you make me!
Would you?
Let him have it, Fate!
You rotten...!
What're you, new? What's with the mask?
That's pretty cocky for some rookie.
Let's see your face!
Dammit! Get him!
Was that Ruinous Strike?
Yeah.
He's done.
One hundred gold coins.
Here you are, Mr. Corpse.
Thanks.
Is it you?
Are you the one responsible for this?
Lady Roxy...
Very well. I understand the situation.
You only struck because
they attacked you first.
Yeah. It was self-defense.
Considering they drew their weapons...
His story matches what
the employees here have to say.
What happens to me now?
While I feel you
may have gone overboard...
I'm partially responsible for
the degradation of Babylon's order.
Given that the holy knight responsible
for keeping the peace was absent,
even if only temporarily...
She means Sir Mason...
There'll be no punishment, this time.
I appreciate that.
I'm willing to overlook this
for the rest of you, too.
All I ask is that you spend
the night in a cell.
Considering you've been up to some trouble,
use it as a chance to reflect.
Huh?
I used to always look up at Lady Roxy...
I guess I've grown?
Excuse me, are you listening?
Yeah! Of course I am!
Liar! You definitely weren't!
Miria...
It's the truth!
And that mask! You're speaking
to Lady Roxy, so take it off!
Stop! This is...
Miria...
Masks are as much a part of
a warrior's gear as anything else.
Hey! Cut it out!
Don't be unreasonable.
There's no need for that.
Thank you.
Now then, might I ask your name?
Corpse.
Your name... is Corpse?
No, it's not.
Shut up!
Dammit! Force of habit...
Well, Mr. Corpse, please try
not to cause any more trouble.
And... I'd advise taking better
care of your appearance.
It's... a bit distracting.
Got it!
What is with him?
He's so lanky, and seems weak at a glance...
But if he clobbered all of them...
What kind of warrior is he?
A good question.
I think she hates me...
That's better than her
figuring out who you are.
Obviously.
Well, as long as you're wearing
that perception-warping mask,
no one will realize that you're Fate.
I know that, but still...
More importantly, even Roxy said
you need to clean yourself up.
Let's buy that scabbard!
We'll need a lot more money
before we do that.
I heard the news! You took out
a gang of ruffians at the exchange?
Y-Yeah.
It's already become news?
I'd love it if you'd take
my gear into battle!
Oh, I never introduced myself, did I?
I'm Jade Stratos.
I've had my own gear shop for three months.
Right...
So, since you haven't made
a name for yourself yet,
you want me to use your
wares as advertising?
Right.
I've been looking for a warrior
who seems like the right one,
so that we could aim
for great heights together.
I-I see...
Would you like to work with me?
With an offer like that,
I've got no reason to refuse.
Then...?
I'm Corpse. Pleasure doing business with you.
Likewise! Thank you for agreeing!
Looks like you've got an exclusive contract.
Now I just affix this...
All done.
Maybe clothes really do make the man.
Shut up.
Uh, I mean, this is better than I had hoped!
That's a relief! Well, it'll be
80 gold coins for the whole set.
Wait, he's charging?
I thought, since this was for advertising...
Uh, never mind.
Oh... in that case, how about half off?
Half...?
I'm spending money
as fast as I can earn it...
You can always go on another hunt.
But first comes food.
This pub looks really busy.
Maybe that's a sign the menu's good.
As long as it's cheap,
I don't really care how it tastes.
What the...?
I can't look away. What is this impulse...?
Looks like you can tell now.
You mean she's...?
You guessed it.
I've been waiting for you to show up, Fate.
But I'm wearing the mask! How?!
And she even knew my name!
Because we're two of a kind, after all.
Then she has a Skill of Deadly Sin!
I'm Eris. Eris of Lust.
Here. Take the mask off.
The perception alteration won't affect me.
Besides...
I want a better look at you.
Dammit!
Oh, sorry about that.
It's a side-effect of the Lust skill.
It gives off an uncontrollable charm effect...
Anyone hit by it,
regardless of age or gender,
can't help but love me.
First, a toast to our meeting.
Y-You said you were waiting for me...
What did you mean?
I've been watching you for a long time.
All the way back to
when you were in the capital.
For that long?
When your Gluttony skill awakened,
I thought about making contact.
But I decided against it, thinking
you'd encounter Greed sooner or later.
If you know about Greed,
then do you know about Myne, too?
Sadly, we've not spoken much.
I'm second generation. I don't know
anyone from the first generation too well.
First generation...?
Right. The Wrath girl and I
don't get along well, anyway.
I mean, considering
how much better endowed I am.
I think she doesn't like that.
Those are definitely big.
Oh, that's right...
Speaking of Myne,
congratulations on slaying Haniel.
She was a tricky one, so I appreciate
you saving me the trouble.
You really do seem to know everything...
I wouldn't go that far.
I don't know who moved the cocoon
to where you found it, for one thing.
The chimera all come
from Galia's capital city.
There's probably a few left, too.
Which will mean real trouble
if they're able to mature...
And with how weak the holy
knight class has become,
I have my doubts as to whether
they'd be able to exterminate them.
Lady Roxy...
Now, then, it's time I get to the point.
What was everything else, then?
This is the real business.
The reason I was waiting for you.
On top of wielding a Skill of Deadly Sin,
I have another identity.
I am a guardian of the kingdom.
A guardian?
Right. I put the kingdom's affairs
above any individual's.
To put it another way,
I'm working towards a better future.
Even something that causes a great loss
today... if, 500 years from now?
A millennium, even? It benefits
the kingdom, then I approve.
What are you getting at?
Roxy Hart.
There appears to be a minor
stampede occurring in eastern Galia.
We'll move to deal with it at once.
Of course!
She's going to die in Galia.
What kind of crap is that?!
You want Lady Roxy dead?
Do you know how the phenomenon
of aggression works?
Don't try and change the subject!
I brought it up because it's related.
When a monster is slain,
its aggression lingers...
That aggression never really goes away,
and over many years,
it builds up bit by bit...
until it gives rise to a crowned beast.
And this same phenomenon...
can occur among humans.
What are you getting at?
Wait—
The oppression, discrimination,
and destitution caused by the holy knights.
All of the aggression aimed at them,
building up within the people...
Let's add to that the death of the only holy
knight beloved by the masses, Roxy Hart.
The swell of aggression born
from her untimely death
will swallow the rest that has
been slowly building up,
fueling the birth of a human
with an all-new type of power.
And among them will be the future pillar
of the kingdom, with an incredible skill.
What do you think? Quite the plan, isn't it?
Her death will guide this
kingdom in a better direction.
There's nothing good that could come
from Lady Roxy's death!
None of the holy knights care
about people the way she does!
Her death would not bring
a single good thing to anyone!
The plan is already in motion.
There's no stopping it.
I don't care what the scheme is,
or who's planning it...
And I don't care who I have to fight.
Onward!
I will protect Lady Roxy!
Trap.
"Trap."